fuelrewards.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Fuel Rewards program

Fuel Rewards® Program Privacy Policy  |  Dining Program Privacy Policy

Last updated as of May 15, 2018

The Excentus Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below) and other information that may be collected by Excentus Corporation (“Excentus”) its affiliates or third parties on behalf of Excentus anytime you interact with Excentus,  its affiliates or such third parties such as when you visit, access, browse or otherwise use the products and services on our websites, mobile applications, mobile websites, or networked equipment (such as our Fuel Rewards® program-branded kiosks or our Fuel Rewards® program-branded tablets or mobile devices that we use to collect information from consumers at participating retailers) ** ** (collectively, “Excentus Sites”).

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain the types of information that Excentus collects from you, what we do with this information, and with whom we share this information. This Privacy Policy includes information that we may collect from you in connection with our Fuel Rewards® program (“Fuel Rewards® Program”). Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, and how we seek to safeguard your Personally Identifiable Information.

#### **Your consent to the Privacy Policy**

By providing information to us or by accessing, browsing or using any of the Excentus Sites or by enrolling in our programs, you acknowledge that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy. You consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information and other information by Excentus pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information and other information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, please do not access, browse, or use the Excentus Sites or provide information to us.

#### **Amendments to the Privacy Policy**

Excentus reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy periodically. Any updates made to this Privacy Policy will be considered effective immediately after the amendments are posted on the Excentus Sites.  Please take a look at the “Last Updated” legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Your access to, browsing of or use of the Excentus Sites, or the submission of any information to us, following such date will be subject to the revised Privacy Policy. 

#### **Jurisdiction**

The Excentus Sites are controlled by us from the United States; accordingly this Privacy Policy, and our collection, use and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information or other information, is governed by U.S. law, and not by the laws of any country, territory or jurisdiction other than the United States. We do not represent or warrant that the Excentus Sites, or any functionality or feature thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction other than that of the United States. Those who choose to download, access or use the Excentus Sites do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules, and regulations. By downloading, accessing, using or submitting any Personally Identifiable Information or other information to the Excentus Sites, users from outside the United States acknowledge that the Excentus Sites are subject to U.S. law, and consent to the transfer of their Personally Identifiable Information or other information to the United States and any other jurisdiction, which may provide a different level of data security than in their country of residence, and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.

#### **Types of Information**

The following are descriptions of the types of information we may acquire from or about you:

  * We may receive and store any Personally Identifiable Information and other information that you provide to us, directly or indirectly, such as by searching on the Excentus Sites, creating an account, enrolling in our programs, redeeming rewards, communicating with us by phone, email, text or otherwise, interacting with Excentus and our affiliates through social media accounts or pages, completing a registration form, Excentus questionnaire or contest entry form, providing reviews, using specific features of your mobile device or otherwise interacting with Excentus and/or the Excentus Sites, and/or by contacting Excentus.
  * We may receive and store Personally Identifiable Information and other information from other sources, such as participating retailers, online merchants, manufacturers, restaurants, bars, clubs and other participants who issue and/or fund rewards, and participating fuel stations who redeem rewards (“Participants”). Examples of information we receive include account information, enrollment information, transactional information, reward issuance or redemption information, geographic information, and other purchase-related information.  We treat the Personally Identifiable Information and other information we receive from other sources in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  We may add this information to any Personally Identifiable Information or other information that you provide to us.
  * We may automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Examples of such information include your browser type, the type of operating system you use, the name of your Internet service provider, your IP address, the referring link through which you accessed the Excentus Sites, pages visited on the Excentus Sites, technical information to assist with fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes, and access times, as well as email addresses, passwords, and the phone number you used to call our customer support number. The most common sources of this information include cookies (including flash cookies as described in more detail below), web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”), pixel tags or clear Graphics Interchange Format files, known as GIFs. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Excentus Sites and services that depend on cookies
  * Your IP address is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. An IP address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Excentus Sites, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels, diagnosing server problems and administering the Excentus Sites. We may also derive your approximate location from your IP address.
  * We may use Flash LSOs (also known as flash cookies) and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of the Excentus Sites.  If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the  _[Website Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)_. You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the  _[Global Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html)_  and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to as "information" on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time).  Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with the Excentus Sites or our online content. 
  * We may collect information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect about you. For example, we may collect information to verify and update mailing addresses.
  * We may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device if you use one of our mobile applications. We use this information to provide you with location-based products and services.
  * To help us make emails more pertinent to you, we may receive confirmation that the email has been opened and which links you click in an email.

#### **Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

“Personally Identifiable Information” means information that identifies you, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, loyalty card number, and payment card number. We use the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to us for such purposes as responding to your requests or questions, providing customer support, improving our services, communicating with you, providing you with information that we believe would interest you, or providing you with information about important functionality changes to our programs and the Excentus Sites. The Personally Identifiable Information enables us to conduct research and perform analysis in order to measure, maintain, protect, develop and improve our products and services and provide anonymous or aggregated reporting. It also enables us to customize and enhance the Excentus Sites, customize the content you see, administer sweepstakes, contests, promotions or surveys and make communications necessary to notify you regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues.

#### **Use of other information**

Other information is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as: browser information; information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies; demographic information and other information provided by you; information from other sources including updated address information; and aggregated information, including aggregated Personally Identifiable Information and aggregated transaction data that has been aggregated so that no single individual is identifiable. **** We use this information for such purposes as understanding how the Excentus Sites are used, to facilitate navigation, to personalize your experience, and to diagnose problems. **** We may use and disclose other information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. In some instances, we may combine other information with Personally Identifiable Information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personally Identifiable Information as long as it is so combined.

#### **Use of Google Analytics**

The Excentus Sites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  This analytical tool uses cookies and similar technologies to help analyze how users use the Excentus Sites.  The information generated about site usage, including visitor IP address, is transmitted to Google.  This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website, compile statistical reports on website activity, and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google offers the ability to opt out from tracking through Google Analytics cookies; for more information, visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

#### **Third Party Advertising Services**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements regarding goods and services that may be of interest to you when you access and use the Excentus Sites and other websites or online services on any of your devices, based on information relating to your access to and use of the Excentus Sites and other websites and online services, as well as on information received from third parties.  To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through use of pixel tags).  They may also use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop.  If you would like to learn more about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit  _http://www.youradchoices.com/learn.aspx_  and  _http://www.aboutads.info/_.  You may download the AppChoices app at [www.aboutads.info/appchoices](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) to opt out in mobile apps. 

#### **Social Media Interactions**

Any information collected by social media services (such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram) in connection with the Excentus Sites (including through social media plugins located on the Excentus Sites) is subject to the applicable social media service’s privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy. For example, Facebook Social Plugins that are currently present on the Excentus Sites may allow Facebook to collect certain information from or about users on the Excentus Sites; the collection, use and disclosure of such information by Facebook is subject to Facebook’s privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy.

If you provide any information to Excentus through a social media service, including through social media plugins located on the Excentus Sites, and including by authorizing such social media service to provide information to Excentus, then we may collect such information, and our use and disclosure of such information will be subject to this Privacy Policy. For example, we may allow you to sign in to your Fuel Rewards® Program account using Facebook Connect, and if you choose to sign in using Facebook Connect, you are authorizing Facebook to provide certain information to Excentus, such as your friend lists, birthday, check-ins, basic profile information and profile picture. We may use, disclose and retain such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including to create and facilitate interactive social experiences, and to bring you products, services and programs from Excentus. 

#### **Publicly displayed information is public**

If you use social media or a bulletin board or chat room on an Excentus Site, you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Information, including Personally Identifiable Information, you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals, including to send you unsolicited messages. Excentus is not responsible for the information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, Excentus will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.  If you are a resident of California, under 18 and a registered user of the Services, you may ask us to remove content or information that you have posted to the Services by writing to support@fuelrewards.com.  Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, as, for example, some of your content may have been reposted by another user.

#### **Disclosure of information**

Information about our members is an important part of our business. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you register a Fuel Rewards® Program card at www.fuelrewards.com, we will provide your Personally Identifiable Information to Shell Oil Products, US and its affiliated companies and their respective advertising, promotions and public relations companies. Use of such Personally Identifiable Information by Shell is subject to the Shell® Fuel Rewards® program Terms & Conditions found [here](https://www.fuelrewards.com/fuelrewards/shellfuelrewards-terms).

If you link your MasterCard, Visa, or American Express branded card (a “Linked Card”) to your Fuel Rewards® Program account, pursuant to your consent when linking your payment card, we will provide to MasterCard, Visa, or American Express, as applicable, (each, a “Payment Card Network”) your Linked Card number and your Fuel Rewards® Program account number solely to enable the applicable Payment Card Network to identify your account and provide transaction information to Excentus regarding transactions made with your Linked Card at merchants who participate in the Fuel Rewards® Program, which may include a unique user identification associated with your Linked Card, as well as transaction amount, date and time, and name and location of merchant. In addition, if you register for an offer that allows you to earn Rewards using your Linked Card (“Card Linked Offer”), MasterCard, Visa or American Express, as applicable, may share with Excentus details (including certain transaction data such as: date, time, merchant name and location, and amount) for your purchases and returns at Participants, so that Excentus can administer your Rewards and administer the Card Linked offer.

Excentus may engage third party marketers (“Third Party Marketers”) to introduce the Fuel Rewards® Program to potential merchants who may want to provide card-link enabled offers to you as part of the Fuel Rewards® Program. Excentus and these merchants may provide such Third Party Marketers transaction data (e.g., merchant ID, merchant location ID, last 4 digits of your registered payment card, dollar amount cleared and settled, and date of the settled transaction). The Third Party Marketer may use this transaction data for the sole purpose of invoicing the merchants for card-link enabled offers you participate in, and may not use this information for any other purpose.

Providing payment card information to us is not required for participation in the Fuel Rewards® Program; however, linking a payment card and providing payment card information is a requirement to receive card-link enabled offers, to participate in Link & Save™ and to participate in the Fuel Rewards® Dining Program

If you enroll and participate in the Dining program as part of the Fuel Rewards® Program, we will provide your Personally Identifiable Information (including your Linked Card number) to Rewards Network Inc. ("Rewards Network") to allow Rewards Network to obtain details about your qualifying transactions from transaction information providers (like Payment Card Networks or Transaction Information Providers), administer the Dining program, and target personalized offers in connection with the Dining program. Use of such Personally Identifiable Information by Rewards Network is subject to the Rewards Network Privacy Policy found here.  To opt out of the Dining program, please log in to your Fuel Rewards account.  Transaction Information Providers shall mean third-party card issuers, providers, platforms, processors, or transaction facilitators or point-of-sale systems.

We provide Personally Identifiable Information and other information to our affiliated companies who may use and disclose the Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We provide Personally Identifiable Information to third party service providers, subcontractors, and agents that work on our behalf to provide certain services. Examples of such services include providing marketing assistance, analyzing data, and providing customer service. These third parties are bound by law or by contract to protect the Personally Identifiable Information and have access to Personally Identifiable Information needed to perform their functions and for no other purpose.

Excentus may report on statistical information relating to the Excentus products and services on the Excentus Sites, through email or other social media including anonymous or aggregated information about consumer and member activity. Such reporting may include displaying your first name, last initial, and city and state of residence.

Excentus may provide aggregated demographic and statistical information to others for purposes of profiling activity, targeting personalized offers, marketing, promotion or similar activities. None of these statistics will identify users by name.

Excentus may disclose Personally Identifiable Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process or applicable law; (b) enforce the Terms and Conditions; (c) respond to claims that any content of an Excentus Site violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Excentus, its users, Members, the public or others.

Excentus may provide your necessary Personally Identifiable Information to third party providers of products and services you request from or through us.

If Excentus becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, restructuring, reorganization or any form of sale or other disposition of some or all of its assets, Personally Identifiable Information may be provided or transferred to the entities involved in such transactions.

#### **Linked Internet websites and other platforms**

The Excentus Sites provide hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to other websites not controlled by us ("Linked Sites"). These Linked Sites may have privacy or data security practices that are different from those provided herein. In addition, if you use a social media platform or your mobile device or other method of communication to interact with Excentus or the Excentus Sites, these applications also have privacy provisions that govern the use of Personally Identifiable Information related to that application. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information or other information collected through Linked Sites, social media platforms, mobile devices or other methods of communication, and we expressly disclaim any and all liabilities related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

The Online Shopping site found at www.shop.fuelrewards.com (“Online Shopping Site”) is operated by Excentus via affiliate marketing networks. Use of the Online Shopping Site and all transactions conducted via the Online Shopping Site are subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies established by Excentus and each individual online merchant. Excentus will have no responsibility or liability with respect to any Rewards earned in connection with a transaction conducted on the Online Shopping Site, or the information collection, usage, disclosure or security practices of each individual online merchant.

The Fuel Rewards Travel site found at www.fuelrewards.com/travel (“Travel Site”) which is accessible via hyperlink from the Excentus Sites, is operated by Priceline Partner Network (“Priceline”), not by Excentus. Use of the Travel Site and all transactions conducted via the Travel Site are subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policy displayed on the Travel Site and the policies established by Priceline. Excentus will have no responsibility or liability with respect to the Travel Site or any activities conducted on the Travel Site, or the information collection, usage, disclosure or security practices of Priceline.

The Dining site found at frndining.com (“Dining Site”) which is accessible via hyperlink from the Excentus Sites, is operated by Rewards Network, Inc. (“Rewards Network”), not by Excentus. Use of the Dining Site and any activities conducted on the Dining Site are subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policy displayed on the Dining Site and the policies established by Rewards Network. Excentus will have no responsibility or liability with respect to the Dining Site or any activities conducted on the Dining Site, or the information collection, usage, disclosure or security practices of Rewards Network.

#### **Browser Do Not Track Signals  **

Although the Excentus Sites currently do not have a mechanism to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals, we do offer our customers choices to manage certain of their preferences that are provided in the previous sections above.  To learn more about browser tracking signals and Do Not Track, please visit _http://www.allaboutdnt.com_.

#### **Protection of your Personally Identifiable Information**

Excentus takes precautions - including administrative, technical, and physical measures - designed to safeguard your Personally Identifiable Information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your Personally Identifiable Information when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser.

If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at 1-888-603-0473.

#### **Access to information**

You may access and correct the Personally Identifiable Information in your user profile by logging into your account and changing the information in your user profile. You may also request changes to your account by clicking the "Contact Us" tab on the Excentus Sites and submitting your request to the Excentus Member Support Helpdesk. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by editing your profile.

#### **Options for communications**

You may receive certain promotional communications from us that may include advertisements from third parties. If, at any time, you wish to no longer receive promotional communications from Excentus, you may opt-out of the receipt of such promotional communications by clicking on the opt-out link provided at the bottom of each email or by emailing our Member Support Helpdesk. Even if you opt-out of receiving promotional communications, you may receive promotional communications that were already in process prior to receipt of our request. We reserve the right to send out certain communications relating to membership information, and administrative messages that are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. Although the primary purpose of these emails is not to provide you with promotional communications, they may contain within them some promotional communications.

#### **Children and Minors**

The Excentus Sites are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals not provide Personally Identifiable Information through the Excentus Sites.

#### **Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Excentus Corporation who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please write to us at:

**Excentus Corporation**  
14241 Dallas Parkway  
Suite 400  
Dallas, Texas, 75254 USA  
Attn:  General Counsel

#### Privacy Questions

If you have questions or concerns about the Excentus Privacy Policy, please click here to contact us. The Excentus Member Support Helpdesk will respond to your inquiry within 60 days.

**Excentus Corporation**  
14241 Dallas Parkway  
Suite 400  
Dallas, Texas, 75254 USA

Copyright © 2012–2018 Excentus Corporation. All rights reserved.

back to top ^ 

* * *

Last updated: October 10, 2019

### PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE

Rewards Network Establishment Services Inc. and its affiliates (individually “we,” “us,” and “our,”) which collaborates with Excentus Corporation (“Rewards Partner”) to provide Fuel Rewards® Dining (the “Program”) through this website or the mobile application (collectively, the “Site”) values your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe how we collect, use, and share information about you via our Site and the Program. By visiting the Site, enrolling in the Program and participating in the Program, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### **Locations of Servers**

### **What We Collect and How We Use It**

Identifiable Information

Information We Collect

Linked Card Information and Transaction Information

Survey Information

Personal Information We Utilize for Contests, Giveaways, Sweepstakes, and Other Promotions

Promotions

Linked Card Updates

IP Addresses

Usage Information and Session Data

Geo-Location

Cookies

Disclosure of Personal Information  
Disclosure of Anonymized Information  
Transfer of Personal Information  
Social Network Plugins  
Third-Party Sites  
Choices for Email and Marketing Campaigns  
Do Not Track  
Retention and Disposal of Information  
Data Security  
Securing Your Personal Information  
Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard  
Reviewing or Changing Your Information  
Information and Security Management Group  
Cancellation and Terminating Your Account  
Contacting Us  
Changes to Our Privacy Policy

### **Lcoation of Servers**

The Site is hosted on servers located in the United States of America and is intended for use by individuals and entities who are United States residents. YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND CONSENT THAT YOUR DATA MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO VARIOUS LOCATIONS AND THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS, AND MAY BE MAINTAINED AND PROCESSED ON COMPUTERS LOCATED OUTSIDE OF YOUR STATE, PROVINCE, COUNTRY, OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL JURISDICTION WHERE THE PRIVACY LAWS MAY NOT BE AS PROTECTIVE AS THOSE IN YOUR JURISDICTION.

### **What We Collect and How We Use It**

#### **Identifiable Information**

You may visit our Site without expressly submitting any information that can be used to identify you (“Personal Information”). However, if you wish to register as a participant in the Program, you will be required to submit Personal Information as further set forth below.

#### **Information We Collect**

If you register in the Program, the Personal Information we collect may include your name, email, mailing address, phone number, and other information requested on the registration page. We will also collect the primary account number for the eligible credit and/or debit card(s) that you use to enroll in the Program (“Linked Card”). We do not collect your Linked Card’s expiration date or card security code. The primary account number is the 14, 15, or 16 digit number that appears on the front of your Linked Card (“Linked Card Number”). We need the Linked Card Number to monitor your Linked Card activity for transactions with participating merchants (“Participating Merchants”) that are eligible for Program rewards. Accordingly, you are authorizing us to obtain and receive information about your Linked Card transactions with Participating Merchants from a payment card network (“Payment Card Network”) such as American Express®, Mastercard®, Visa®, Discover®, or a payment card processor.

We may also collect Personal Information about you from Rewards Partner or a bank issuing a credit card on Rewards Partner’s behalf that automatically enrolls you in the Program as a benefit (collectively, “Rewards Partner Information”). If you are automatically enrolled with Rewards Network by Rewards Partner, Rewards Network will only receive, maintain and use the Rewards Partner Information that Rewards Network needs to operate the Program.

You may need to create a user name and password for your Program account with us. We may assign you a unique identification number so that we may more easily identify you and your transactions.

You have the option to also provide us with the month and day of special dates (e.g., birthday, anniversary), dining preferences, and information regarding your personal accounts and/or profiles on third-party social networking sites such as Facebook® and Twitter®, as further described below.

Additionally, we or Rewards Partner (or a non-affiliated third-party supplier, vendor, or contractor on our behalf or on behalf of the Rewards Partner) may collect Personal Information when you send us an inquiry, comment, or request relating to the Program, including any email or mailing address or telephone number you provide, and will use the information you have provided to respond. We may also add this information to your Program profile and use such information as contemplated in this Privacy Policy.

We or Rewards Partner (or a non-affiliated third-party supplier, vendor, or contractor on our behalf or on behalf of the Rewards Partner) use your Personal Information only to operate the Program, including to send you emails, mailings, or other forms of communications (that may be real-time) that relate to the Program, Participating Merchants.

#### **Linked Card Information and Transaction Information**

Program, including determining your eligibility for rewards and applying rewards, requesting that you receive rewards, and compliance with this Privacy Policy, the Program [Terms of Use](https://www.fuelrewards.com/fuelrewards/terms-conditions#dining) and any other applicable terms and conditions. We may disclose the Linked Card Number to Rewards Partner, Payment Card Networks, payment card processors, and payment card issuers, as well as non-affiliated third-party suppliers, vendors, or contractors that we have engaged to help us operate the Program.

We will know when you conduct a transaction with a Participating Merchant. We will collect information about that transaction, including a unique Program identification number, the date and time of your transaction, the amount of your transaction, the name and location of the Participating Merchant, and the Linked Card used for that transaction. We receive this information from Payment Card Networks. We may provide all or a portion of the information collected to a Rewards Partner or a Rewards Partner’s non-affiliated third-party suppliers, vendors, or contractors so that we and/or Rewards Partner can facilitate and administer the Program. You may receive real-time notification about the sharing of your transaction data. We may also use your transaction information to generate internal financial reporting and analysis regarding our business and for external reporting of anonymized data to market our business and the Program to third parties, including potential Participating Merchants and potential rewards partners.

We use the transaction data that we receive to match your transactions at Participating Merchants with available rewards and otherwise for Program rewards administration. In some cases, a Participating Merchant’s payment card processor may experience a lag time (approximately 24 hours) between when a credit and/or debit card is linked to a Program account and when the payment card processor is able to identify and provide us with the dining transaction data associated with that Linked Card. If you believe that you are eligible for rewards for dining at a Participating Merchant, and those rewards have not registered in your Program account within 10 days of the dine, please contact the Program’s Member Services at (855) 694-3463. We reserve the right to require that you provide a receipt from the Participating Merchant or documents reasonably required by us to evidence an eligible transaction in order to receive your reward.

By enrolling in and participating in the Program, you are authorizing us and Participating Merchants, Payment Card Networks, and payment card processors to obtain, provide, and use transaction information related to your purchases (such as date, time and amount) at Participating Merchants in order to calculate rewards, redeem rewards, and facilitate and make the Program available. You also authorize us to, in our reasonable discretion, collect location data using your device to provide you with recommendations based on your location and past dining activity, analyze your general dining patterns and stores that you visit, and also aggregate this data to help understand general Program member patterns and trends, which we may share with third parties with our discretion.

#### **Survey Information**

Following your matched transaction and the processing of any reward, we may send you an email to complete a survey regarding your transaction. When you activate the survey link, you will be taken to a web page operated by us. We (or a non-affiliated third-party supplier, vendor, or contractor on our behalf or on behalf of the Rewards Partner) may collect on an anonymized basis your computer's IP address or use cookies to collect aggregated, anonymized data related to your survey responses. We may share the anonymized survey information with the applicable Participating Merchant. We may also aggregate your survey response with other survey responses for the applicable Participating Merchant and make those results available to other participants in our rewards programs.

For certain qualifying purchases, you may be required to complete the survey in order to earn rewards.

All reviews, surveys, comments, feedback, and other information about your dining experiences, Participating Merchants, or participation in the Program that you choose to disclose, submit, or convey via the Site (which we refer to collectively as "Comments") may be reprinted, used, displayed, redistributed, shared, transmitted, excerpted, modified, and/or disseminated (in whole or in part) by us. Your Comments must comply with our [Review Guidelines](https://dining.fuelrewards.com/guidelines.htm) We reserve the right to remove any Comments that are inappropriate.

Your provision of Comments to us constitutes a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such Comments throughout the world in any media.

You warrant that: (i) any use of Comments by us will not violate any right of any third party; and (ii) any Comments are not libelous, unlawful, or obscene.

#### **Personal Information We Utilize for Contests, Giveaways, Sweepstakes, and Other Promotions**

You also may have the option to voluntarily provide us or Rewards Partner, as well as non-affiliated third-party suppliers, vendors, or contractors working on our behalf, with Personal Information in connection with participating in contests, giveaways, sweepstakes, and other promotions, or in connection with completing surveys for us. This information may be added to your member profile, and may be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy or the notice provided at the time of collection. Please review the terms and conditions for such opportunities carefully.

#### **Linked Card Updates**

If your card number changes, you are responsible for updating your Linked Card in your account profile. In some cases, we may receive updated credit and/or debit card numbers associated with your Linked Card from payment card processors or Payment Card Networks. If we receive this information, we will update the Linked Card with the new credit and/or debit card number that we receive, and we will use it to operate the Program as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### **IP Addresses**

We collect IP address information from any visitor to the Site. We log IP addresses for system administrative purposes only. IP addresses are not used for identification. This information helps us determine how often different areas of the Site are visited. We do not link IP addresses to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### **Usage Information and Session Data**

When you visit the Site or click on a link in an e-mail from one of our Participating Merchants, we may collect usage information ("Session Data"). Session Data may include browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, platform, and what Participating Merchants you look at. We may use Session Data for a variety of reasons, including to better understand things like how the Site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at and look at specific pages, and the length and frequency of stays at our Site. We disclose such Session Data to our Participating Merchants to provide proof of attribution metrics.

#### **Geo-Location**

We may have the ability to collect location data and provide you with push notifications based on your location and past dining activity. We utilize location information to provide you with more relevant location-based restaurant choices, track your general dining patterns and stores that you visit, and also aggregate this data to help understand general Program member patterns and trends, which we may share with third parties in our discretion. You are agreeing that we can collect and use your location data and can continue to do so until you turn off your location settings.

Your device may allow you to disable the collection of location data and push notifications by accessing your device’s application or notification settings. If you do not want us to have access to your location, you may change your location settings. You are agreeing that we can continue to collect location data until you turn off data collection in your device. We have no responsibility or liability for the functions of location settings within any device.

#### **Cookies**

Like most sites, we use cookies on the Site to collect Session Data and persistent data for several purposes, such as to personalize and improve your individual viewing experiences, track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage statistical information in order to constantly improve the quality of the Site, and for other purposes, including to better understand things like how the Site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at and look at specific pages, and the length and frequency of stays at our Site. We use two different types of cookies on our Site:

  * **Session cookies** track the user's progression through the Site and session data for a single visit. These cookies enable us to follow the user as they progress from one page to another. Your session cookies expire at the end of your browser session. In addition, if you leave your browser open for a prolonged period, they are set to automatically expire.
  * **Persistent cookies** are stored on your device between browser sessions, allowing us to remember you and your preferences on the Site. We may use a persistent cookie to remember such information as your user name, name, preferred dining area, favorite restaurants, and Session Data.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit.

We use Google Analytics in order to analyze traffic and performance related to the Site. To learn how Google uses data when you use our Site, visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

#### **Disclosure of Personal Information**

We use your Personal Information and share it with Rewards Partner, Payment Card Networks, and payment card processors to solely operate the Program. We also disclose Session Data to our Participating Merchants, as discussed above. We do not sell Personal Information to any third party and we will not, without your prior express consent, disclose your Personal Information to any third party for them to market to you directly. For example, we may invite you to participate in a survey or special promotional program offered by a non-affiliated third party. Your choice to participate in such a survey or promotional program will indicate your consent for us to share your Personal Information with non-affiliated third parties in connection with the survey or promotional program. If you consent to such disclosure, any information that you provide to the third parties will be controlled by that party's privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy.

We or Rewards Partner may disclose information that we may have, identifiable or not, as necessary for defending and bringing legal actions; if required by a government authority or legal process; when we or Rewards Partner believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation or prosecution of suspected or actual illegal activity; or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable.

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, use, and disclose any information collected on this Site (as described in this Privacy Policy) for any purpose not prohibited by this Privacy Policy, applicable law, or an applicable agreement.

#### **Disclosure of Anonymized Information**

We may share anonymized information about you that is not reasonably identifiable to you with our affiliates, rewards partners, Participating Merchants, and other third parties in our discretion. Such information could be used, for example, to provide us with statistical or other analysis and to market our business, the Program or both. This information is de-identified and cannot reasonably be used to identify you personally. This information is most often aggregated demographic and statistical information (such as information derived from use of our Site or your participation in any Program) and information submitted in connection with restaurant reviews or surveys that you submit to us.

#### **Transfer of Personal Information**

We reserve the right to transfer all information and data in our possession, custody, or control to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other sale of all or a portion of our assets. Any acquirer will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

#### **Social Network Plugins**

The Site utilizes plugins from various social networking sites (such as Facebook® and Twitter®) to allow you to share and post materials between your Program account with us and your social network accounts. Social networks may use cookies and other tools to collect data regarding your browsing activity. Please be advised that your browser-related information and personal information collected in connection with your use of the social media plug-ins will be transferred to such social networking sites and will be used in accordance with each social networking site’s privacy policy. Your browser-related information may be transferred regardless of whether or not you use the plugin.

If you give us permission to use and post information about your restaurant visits, restaurant reviews, and other activities on our social networking accounts or your social networking accounts, usage of that social network site is governed by and subject to the privacy policy of that third-party social network site and any privacy settings that are available on that third-party site.

#### **Third-Party Sites**

We neither own nor control any third-party sites that may be accessible through the Site, and do not control the privacy policies of such third parties. As a result, we assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties. We suggest that you review the privacy policy of any third-party site before submitting information to them.

#### **Choices for Email and Marketing Communications**

You may opt out of receiving Program emails from us. However, doing so will affect your eligibility for all or some Program benefits. You may not opt out of receiving administrative emails related to your account except by terminating your Program participation.

If you do not wish to receive email communications from us, you can unsubscribe from the link in the email you received, change your selections within the Account Information section, or indicate your preferences within a direct communication to us. You may also email us if you wish to unsubscribe, but for your security, please do not send credit and/or debit card information via email.

#### **Do Not Track**

Because there is not an industry or legal standard for recognizing or honoring Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals, we do not respond to them at this time.

#### **Retention and Disposal of Information**

We retain your information as long as we determine it is required for the operation of our business and Program, and to meet legal, regulatory, and other requirements.

We take reasonable steps to ensure that information is disposed of securely when we no longer require such data.

#### **Data Security**

We take commercially reasonable steps to maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your information. These safeguards may include data encryption, access authorization, firewalls, and physical access control to our data centers. We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving identifiable information. We maintain PCI DSS compliance. You can find our [listing](https://www.visa.com/splisting/viewSPDetail.do?coName=Rewards%20Network&HeadCountryList=U.S.A.&pageInfo=106%3B30%3BASC%3BcoName) on the Visa Global Registry of Service Providers.

We maintain a Service Organization Control (SOC) 3 report. This assessment of our security practices enables you and your stakeholders to validate that we have obtained independent auditor assurance, which attests to our alignment with the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA) Security Trust Principles. We may elect in the future to assess our security practices through a standard other than SOC, and we will in any case maintain and routinely test our controls related to the security, integrity, confidentiality, and privacy of the information we collect, store, and process.

#### **Securing Your Personal Information**

Rewards Network and the Program will never ask you for personal information, including financial information, via unsolicited telephone calls, emails, postal mailers, or fax transmissions.

Specifically, Rewards Network and the Program will never send you unsolicited requests for the following types of Personal Information: (i) username or password; (ii) email address; (iii) social security number; (iv) credit and/or debit card number; (v) credit card expiration date or card security code; (vi) bank account numbers; or (vii) names of your family members. This list is provided for illustrative purposes only and is not intended to include all categories of information that may be the subject of an unsolicited request for Personal Information.

Any request for personal information of this nature in a conversation not initiated by you should be considered suspicious, even if the communication includes Rewards Network or the Program logos, links to websites that look “like” the Program, or a request for you to take immediate action, such as verifying your account information. Unsolicited communications of this type are often fraudulent “phishing” communications, and could be an attempt to acquire your sensitive personal information for malicious reasons.

#### **Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard**

In order to protect your Personal Information, Rewards Network complies with the security standards (PCI DSS) required by the [PCI Security Standards Council](https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/).

The Council was founded in 2006 by five prominent payment brands — including American Express®, Discover Financial Services®, JCB International®, Mastercard®, and Visa, Inc.®. This global forum is responsible for the development, management, education, and awareness of security standards for credit and debit cards.

PCI DSS applies to all entities involved in payment card processing. This includes retailers where consumer purchases are made, payment card processors, credit card issuers, and service providers. Rewards Network continually reviews its payment card security practices to ensure that those practices satisfy the requirements of the most current version of the PCI DSS compliance standards.

If you suspect that you have received a phishing or other type of fraudulent communication, you should not: (i) click on any links in the offending email; (ii) open any attachments related to the communication; (iii) call any telephone numbers provided in the communication; or (iv) follow instructions contained in the communication. If the phishing or other fraudulent communication purports to be associated with the Program, you should report the communication to Rewards Network by sending an email to [security@rewardsnetwork.com](mailto:security@rewardsnetwork.com). You should attach the unsolicited communication to your email report. If you received the communication by postal mail, rather than by email, you should photograph any mailer, letter, and envelope received and attach those materials to the email report that you send to Rewards Network.

#### **Reviewing or Changing Your Information**

You can contact us (by email, telephone, or postal mail) to request access and/or modify any information that we have for you, or otherwise modify your preferences pertaining to our marketing communications. To review, change, or update your information:

  * **Online:** When the Program Site is available, sign in to your account to be taken to the Account Center. Click on the “Profile” link on the left side of the homepage. From here, you will be able to change your Personal Information or modify your communication preferences.
  * **By postal mail:** Please include your email address and mail your request to us at Rewards Network Establishment Services Inc., 2 N. Riverside Plaza, Suite 200, Chicago, IL 60606, Attn: Member Services.
  * **By phone:** Members may contact Fuel Rewards Dining Member Services toll-free at (855) 694-3463.
  * **By email:** support@fuelrewards.com.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections or granting access to your information.

#### **Information Security Management Group**

We have instituted the Information Security Management Group (ISMG), which is responsible for ensuring that the protection of your Personal Information, including your Linked Card, and other information collected is carried out in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The following person serves as the contact for the ISMG:

General Counsel  
Rewards Network  
2 N. Riverside Plaza  
Suite 200  
Chicago, IL 60606  
(312) 521-6767  

#### **Cancellation and Terminating Your Account**

If you do not agree to have your information collected, shared and used as described in this Privacy Policy, you may terminate your Program account at any time by contacting us at (855) 694-3463 or visiting the “Manage Cards” portion of the Account Center while logged in, and deleting all remaining credit and/or debit cards from your account.

If you no longer consent to this Privacy Policy and our collection and maintenance of this information, you must un-enroll from the Program. If you elect to un-enroll or are otherwise deactivated from the Program, we will also need to disclose that information to Rewards Partner, non-affiliated third-party suppliers, vendors, contractors, payment card issuers, payment card processors, and Payment Card Networks as necessary to allow them to remove you from the Program.

#### **Contact Us**

For any questions, or to request further information regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@RewardsNetwork.com](mailto:legal@RewardsNetwork.com)

#### **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account and/or possibly through a notice on our Site’s home page. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Site and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

back to top ^ 

* * *
